We are here with the iconic, the legendary Vanessa Williams, and it's time to go for
the record.
You said that when you were growing up and you were in high school in New York, you didn't
hang out with the white kids at the school.
Y'all had your Jack and Jill parties.
Y'all had your own situations.
Tell me a song that reminds you of that time.
Reasons, live version, hands down.
That was the basement jam that everybody would speck out who they're going to be slow
dancing with.
Lights would be super dark, and that's when everybody would go and do their grinding.
So that's reasons why everybody sang along.
That was the jam.
You talked about your mom, and you live next door to your mom.
You're spending Mother's Day with your mom.
What's a song that reminds you of mom?
Ooh, it would have to be either Roberta Flack, First Time Ever I Saw Your Face, or Johnny
Mathis, chances are.
What do you feel like is a lesson that you learned from your mom that you still keep with
you today?
She said early on, you're going to have to do more than everyone else just to be considered
equal because of who you are and your skin.
I don't know whether that made me an overachiever or whether she made sure that I was in every
program available that made me an overachiever.
But that was just something that to be noticed, you're going to have to do, you're going to
have to exceed and excel and everything just to be noticed.
And it's still, I think it's still apropos.
We are, we are, we are.